sweepstakes.com 2009-03-10

# Sweepstakes.com Privacy Policy

**SWEEPSTAKES.COM PRIVACY POLICY**

 _Policy Last Revised: October 1, 2008_

The following sets forth the policies for the collection and use of personally identifiable information (“Information”) by Sweepstakes.com Acquisition Group, LLC (“Sweepstakes.com”) in connection with its operation of its Web site located at http://www.sweepstakes.com (the “Site”), and supersedes any previous statement of such policies.  Sweepstakes.com takes its obligations regarding privacy very seriously, and it wants to ensure users are fully informed about the Information they are providing to it.

 _Collection of Information_ : In connection with the Site, Sweepstakes.com may collect Information in the following ways: __

·          Through forms filled out by a user on the Site

·         Through Information provided by a user in connection with surveys and prize promotion entries

·         Through entries made by the user in blogs and other forums on the Site

·         Through the maintenance and analysis of Web server logs

·         Via e-mail and other communications between a user and Sweepstakes.com

·         Through the use by Sweepstakes.com of third-party databases from which user Information is extracted and combined with Information obtained by Sweepstakes.com through other means.

Tracking Technologies: Sweepstakes.com uses cookies to store your User ID. We link the USER ID to your database profile, which contains you personally identifiable information you submit while on our site, when a user Opts into a Co-Registration ad or submits any forms your personally identifiable information is being sent to that third party. In addition, your personally Identifiable information is sent to carefully screened third parties to fill in forms and/or make the advertising work properly. The Personally Identifiable Information will not be shared until a valid submit has occurred. We use both session ID cookies and persistent cookies. A session ID cookie expires when you close you browser. We use session cookies to make it easier for you to navigate our site. A persistent cookie remains on your hard drive for an extended period. We use cookies on point of collection pages of e-mail address but we do not use them in e-mails. We use cookies on the point of collection pages so that you may save your login and password. 

Sweepstakes.com may also connect demographic information provided by users via cookies, single-pixel GIF image files (also called “Web beacons”), Web server log analysis and other similar technological means. Information collected by means of such tracking technologies includes site analytics and may be used to track site trends and enhance the user experience, and may be shared with third parties

You can remove persistent cookies by following directions provided in your Internet browser’s Help section. Internet Explorer users can [click here](http://windowshelp.microsoft.com/windows/en-us/search.aspx?=&qu=cookies). If you reject cookies, you may still use our site, but your ability to use some areas of our site, such as contests or surveys, will be limited.

To the extent third parties may place advertising on the Site, such third parties may utilize cookies or other technological means within the advertising to collect and utilize non-personally identifiable information.  Sweepstakes.com is not responsible for information collected by third parties in this manner, nor for the collection or use of Information by other sites to which the Site is linked.

 _Types of Information Collected by Sweepstakes.com_ : The following types of Information about a user are among those that may be collected by Sweepstakes.com in connection with the Site: __

·          Name

·         Postal address

·         E-mail address

·         Telephone number

·         Cell phone number

·         Gender

·         Facsimile number

·         Income range

·         Personal interests

·         Age

·         Date of birth

·         Number of children

·         Purchase intent

·         Education level

·         Marital status

·         IP Address

·         Referring site

·         Establishments visited

·         Other technical information collected by the Site’s servers

We use third party software to verify information that is provided to us, including but not limited to e-mail address and postal address. This is necessary to ensure that you can be reached in the event that you win, to better target our advertising and to provide pertinent offers in which we think you would be interested. 

_No Collection of Information from Children_ : The Site is not intended for users under the age of 18, nor does Sweepstakes.com knowingly collect or retain Information in connection with the Site from children under the age of 13.

 _Use of Information_ : Sweepstakes.com may use Information collected in connection with the Site in the following ways:

·         To provide requested information, products and services to users via the Site or through other online or offline channels

·         To enable users to enter prize promotions and receive prizes from Sweepstakes.com and/or third parties

·         To improve the user experience with the Site

·         In connection with the operation of the Site

·         For users to obtain information and offers for products and services offered by Sweepstakes.com as well as selected third parties via the Site or through other online or offline channels. 

If a registrant indicates interest by opting in to receiving offers from Sweepstakes.com and/or selected third parties on the Registration page or Edit Profile page, they and we will occasionally send information on products, services, special deals, and promotions. Out of respect for the privacy of our registrants, we present the option not to receive these types of communications on both the initial registration page as well as the Edit Profile page.

In order to do the foregoing, Sweepstakes.com uses other trusted third parties to provide services including, but not limited to: technical development, operations management, web hosting, e-mail service provision, ad serving, data validation, sweepstakes game administration, advertising on our site.  When you sign up for Sweepstakes.com the Site, we may share all of the information you provide as necessary for the third party to provide that service. These third parties are prohibited from using your personally identifiable information for any other purposes. We may also share Information with selected third parties that offer products and services about which you may wish to hear, based on your stated preferences.  Sweepstakes.com will use commercially reasonable efforts to limit use of the Information by such third parties to the specific uses set forth above. Sweepstakes.com also utilizes electronic and physical security to reduce the risk of improper access to or manipulation of Information during transmission and storage, but cannot guarantee the security or integrity of the Information and shall have no liability for breaches of security or integrity or third party interception in transit.

The security of personal information and email address is important to Sweepstakes.com.  When a registrant user enters personal information on our Registration form and Edit Profile page, we encrypt the transmission of that information using secure socket layer technology (SSL).  

Sweepstakes.com follows generally accepted industry standards to protect the personal information and e-mail address submitted to us, both during transmission and once we receive it. No method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure, however. Therefore, while we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your personal information and e-mail address, we cannot guarantee its absolute security.

Sweepstakes.com will use framing technology to make it appear that you are still on Sweepstakes.com when in fact you will be interacting with a third party site in the lower frame. Those third parties are currently Prospectiv and Interactive. These framed sites are securely passed using SSL technology you personal information. You will see your personal information pre-populated on their offer pages. This is to facilitate ease of use for their offers to you. If you do not want these offers there is a skip button or other features on the page which will allow you to bypass their offers and receive your entry to the Sweepstakes.com sweepstake. Per our contract with these companies, your information will only be used in conjunction with these offers at the time you go through them. That information will be deleted when you are done with your sweepstakes path.

We reserve the right to disclose your personally identifiable information and email address as required by law and when we believe that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights and/or comply with a judicial proceeding, court order, or legal process served on our Web site. Sweepstakes.com may also disclose Information to affiliated entities in connection with a merger, acquisition, asset purchase or sale of or by Sweepstakes.com, or to protect the interests or safety of Sweepstakes.com, its customers, or other visitors to the Site.

 _Opting Out from Receiving Offers_ : At any time, a user may opt out from receiving future e-mail offers from Sweepstakes.com or third party e-mail marketers through the user’s profile on the Site or by following the instructions contained within each e-mail marketing communication. To opt out from receiving future non-e-mail offers from Sweepstakes.com or third party marketers, send a message via e-mail to privacy_manager@sweepstakes.com or via postal mail to Sweepstakes.com Privacy Manager, 123 Newbury St., Second Floor, Boston, MA 02116.  Such opting out will not apply to any communications from third parties to whom Sweepstakes.com may have previously provided Information regarding the user. Third parties’ use of the Information is subject to such parties’ own privacy policies, for which Sweepstakes.com shall not be responsible.

 _Access to Personally Identifiable Information, E-mail Address and Other Information_ : All users who provide their Information to Sweepstakes.com may modify and correct certain of such Information through their personal profile on the Site. If your personally identifiable information or e-mail address changes, you may correct or update it by making the change on the Edit Profile page, which is accessible by logging in to your account and then clicking to the My Sweepstakes page. Once on the My Sweepstakes page, click “View & Edit Your Profile”. Once there, click “Edit My Profile”. If you want to cancel or deactivate your membership you may do so by contacting Customer Service through this online form http://www.sweepstakes.com/Company/Help.aspx or by contacting us by postal mail at Sweepstakes.com Customer Service, 123 Newbury St., Second Floor, Boston, MA 02116.   _Tell-A-Friend:_  If you choose to use our referral service to tell a friend about our site, we will ask you for your friend’s name and e-mail address.  We will automatically send your friend a one-time e-mail inviting him or her to visit the site.  Sweepstakes.com does not store this information ut uses this information for the sole purpose of sending this one-time e-mail.

Other Information: If you provide any form of user-generated content on Sweepstakes.com, by answering questions, using a bulletin board, blog, or chat room, you should be aware that any personally identifiable information you submit there can be read, collected, or used by other users of these forums, and could be used to send you unsolicited messages.  We are not responsible for the personally identifiable information you choose to submit in these forums.

 _Your California Privacy Rights_: Beginning on January 1, 2005, California Civil Code Section 1798.83 permits customers of Sweepstakes.com who are California residents to request certain information regarding Sweepstakes.com’s disclosure of personal information to third parties for such third parties’ direct marketing purposes. To make such a request, please write to: privacy_manager@sweepstakes.com.

 _Changes to this Privacy Policy_ : Sweepstakes.com reserves the right to revise and update this Privacy Policy, including but not limited to its e-mail practices, at any time. Any such revisions will be effective on the date of posting to the Site, and will apply to all information collected by Sweepstakes.com both prior to and following the effective date. Your use of the Site following any such revisions will be deemed your acceptance of such revisions. If we make material changes to this policy, we will notify you here, by e-mail, or by means of a notice on our home page. Users should periodically visit this page to review the current policies with regard to Information. ****

Contact Information: To contact Sweepstakes.com regarding this Privacy Policy, please e-mail the Sweepstakes.com Privacy Manager at[privacy_manager@sweepstakes.com](mailto:privacy_manager@sweepstakes.com) or write to the Sweepstakes.com Privacy Manager at Privacy Manager, Sweepstakes.com, 123 Newbury St., Second Floor, Boston, MA 02116.
